Guide to the Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative Records, 1864-1956; Series III
  - Charles Hyde Warren and Edmund W. Sinnott
    - Correspondence, 1922-1956
      - Biological Sciences, President's Committee on the: minutes and preliminary reports, 1938-1939 (Box 41, Folder 385)
      - Biology See: folder 435, Human Biology and Ecology
      - Botany, Department of: correspondence re: reorganization, 1939-1940 (Box 41, Folder 386)
      - Budget for the Dean's Fund, 1932-1933 (Box 41, Folder 387)
      - Budget, office expenses, 1933-1944 (Box 41, Folder 388)
      - Bursar, 1942-1945 (Box 41, Folder 389)
      - Bursary office, miscellaneous matters, 1938-1945 (Box 42, Folder 390)
      - Chemistry, 1926-1928 (Box 42, Folder 391)
      - Chittenden, Russell Henry, 1930, 1943-1945 (Box 42, Folder 392)
      - Chittenden (Russell H.) Prize, 1944, 1946 (Box 42, Folder 393)
      - Class of 1896S, Committee on University Affairs See: folder 399, Richard P. Dana
      - Class of 1901S Scholarship, 1911, 1933, 1941, 1951 (Box 42, Folder 394)
      - Correspondence courses for men in the Armed Services, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 395)
      - Course of Study, Committee on the, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 396)
      - Curriculum, plan for possible elimination of courses in the event of an emergency, 1941 (Box 42, Folder 397)
      - Daggett, Susan E.: correspondence re: photograph of brother Ellsworth Daggett (1864S), 1925 (Box 42, Folder 398)
      - Dana, Richard P., Chairman of the Committee on University Affairs of the Class of 1896S, 1922-1924 (Box 42, Folder 399)
      - Danbury Scholarship, 1919, 1921 (Box 42, Folder 400)
      - Day, Frank Miles: agreement with Sheffield Scientific School to be Supervising Architect to Yale University for the term 1913 Jul-1916 Jul, 1913 December 26 (Box 42, Folder 401)
      - Dean's Committee: correspondence and minutes, 1939-1945 (Box 42, Folder 402)
      - Division C, Committee on: recommendations for better organization of Science in the University, 1929-1930 (Box 42, Folder 403)
      - Ecology See: folder 435, Human Biology and Ecology
      - Educational Planning, Committee on: minutes, 1939-1945 (Box 42, Folder 404)
      - Educational Planning: Committee on: reports, 1936-1944 (Box 42, Folder 405 - 406)
      - Educational Planning, Committee on: department analyses, Circa 1940 (Box 42, Folder 407)
      - Engineering See: folders 471-472, Committee to Investigate the Problems of Science and Engineering at Yale
      - Engineering Association See: folder 498, Yale Engineering Association See also: folders 408-413, Engineering Camp, East Lyme
      - Engineering Camp, East Lyme
        - Agreement with E.G. Watrous for sale and removal of trees from the camp, 1938 November 17 (Box 43, Folder 408)
        - Building information, 1926 (Box 43, Folder 409)
        - Correspondence with the Niantic Manufacturing Company and others re: construction of a dam on Powers Lake, 1913 (Box 43, Folder 410)
        - Property lines question, 1915, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 411)
        - Tax matters, 1924, 1927, 1933-1934 (Box 43, Folder 412)
        - Tax question, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 413)
      - Engineering, Division of, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 414)
      - Engineering School: general information, 1932 (Box 43, Folder 415)
      - Engineering, Special Committee on, to investigate reorganizing Sheffield Scientific School and establishing a separate engineering school at Yale, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 416)
      - Enrollment and Scholarship, Committee on: admissions and scholarship information, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 417)
      - Examinations, comprehensive: report re: investigation of the question of introducing such exams into Sheffield Scientific School, undated (Box 43, Folder 418)
      - Exchange Professorship: The Committee of American Universities on Exchange with France of Professors of Engineering and Applied Science, C.H. Warren, Yale representative, 1926-1928 (Box 43, Folder 419)
      - Faculty of Arts and Sciences: correspondence, memos, minutes of meetings, 1923, 1933, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 420)
      - Fees, 1939-1942 (Box 43, Folder 421)
      - Fisher, H.B. See: folder 482, Dean's Committee on Social Research
      - Ford (William Ebenezer) Fund (in honor of the professor of Mineralogy), 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 422)
      - Fraternities, 1925, 1927, 1930, 1943-1945 (Box 43, Folder 423)
      - Fraternities, Inter-Society Council, 1927, 1930, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 424)
      - French Department, 1929, 1932, 1939-1940 (Box 43, Folder 425)
      - Freshman Year Program, 1929, 1933-1944 (Box 43, Folder 426)
      - German language, 1944, undated (Box 43, Folder 427)
      - Gibbs, Josiah Willard
        - Anniversary of the one-hundredth year of his birth: publication, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 428)
        - Comittee on the Collected Works of Gibbs, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 429)
        - Gibbs Fund, 1934, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 430)
        - Gibbs Hall of Fame election: correspondence, 1950-1955 (Box 44, Folder 431)
      - Graduate Record Examination Handbook, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 432)
      - 144 Grove Street: correspondence, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 433)
      - Hay, Southard See; folder 394, Class of 1901S Scholarship
      - Honors, Comittee on, P.F. Smith, Chairman, 1926-1927 (Box 44, Folder 434)
      - Human Biology and Ecology Program, 1951-1952 (Box 44, Folder 435)
      - Humanities, Committee to Consider the Position of the, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 436)
      - Industrial Administration and Engineering, Department of, 1936 (Box 44, Folder 437)
      - Inventories, 1924, 1929, 1931-1932, 1934, 1944-1955 (Box 44, Folder 438)
      - Investments Diversification Plan, 1944-45 (Box 44, Folder 439)
      - Johnson (Treat Bladwin) Fellowship Fund, 1942, 1945 (Box 44, Folder 440)
      - Knights of Colombus Scholarships, 1919 (Box 44, Folder 441)
      - Lyman Lectures, 1921 (Box 44, Folder 442)
      - McCormick, Vance C.: correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 44, Folder 443)
      - Manufacturer's Association of Connecticut, 1926-1927 (Box 44, Folder 444)
      - Manufacturer's Association of Connecticut: Industrial Research Bureau: material re: cooperative research, 1922-1924, 1926 (Box 44, Folder 445 - 446)
      - Marine Historical Association, Inc., Mystic, Connecticut: correspondence re: the permanent loan of the old South Sheffield Half tower clock, and two other items to the Association, 1953, 1955 (Box 44, Folder 447)
      - Marking system, revision of, 1932-1933, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 448)
      - Mathematics, Department of See also: floder 473, Division of Science and Mathematics, 1928, 1933-1935 (Box 44, Folder 449)
      - Metallurgy, [1930?] (Box 44, Folder 450)
      - Military Science and Tactics, Department of, 1941 (Box 44, Folder 451)
      - Miller, John A. (1915S): correspondence re: a proposal to write a history of Sheffiefd Scientific School's first one hundred years, 1947 (Box 44, Folder 452)
      - Moore (Edward J.) Scholarship Loan Fund, 1906, 1937, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 453)
      - Moulton, F.R. See: folder 375, American Association for the Advancement of Science
      - Natural Preserve, Committee on Yale: correspondence, financial material, minutes, 1950-1953 (Box 45, Folder 454)
      - Natural Science See: folder 473, Division of Science and Mathematics
      - Naval Science and Tactics, Department of, 1935-1945 (Box 45, Folder 455)
      - Navy College Training Program (Navy V-12 Program), 1943 (Box 45, Folder 456)
      - Navy College Training Program (Navy V-12 Program), Physics, 1943 (Box 45, Folder 457)
      - New Haven College Y.M.C.A., 1927-1930, 1935-1941 (Box 45, Folder 458)
      - New York Trust Company: resolution governing Sheffield Scientific School custodian account, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 459)
      - North Sheffield Hall: correspondence between R.H. Chittenden and S.W. Dudley re: "potato patch" legend, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 460)
      - North Sheffield Hall: correspondence, re: [illegible] system, 1906 (Box 45)
      - Penfield Prize (Box 45, Folder 461)
      - Physical Science See: folder 473, Division of Science and Mathematics
      - Physics, Department of: general information See also: folder 473, Division of Science and Mathematics, 1951-1952 (Box 45, Folder 462)
      - Physics: list of physical apparatus and books transferred from Winchester Hall to Sloane Physical Laboratory, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 463)
      - Pratt (Francis A.) Scholarship Fund, 1927, 1929, 1931 (Box 45, Folder 464)
      - Preparation for War Service Committee: minutes and records, 1942-1943 (Box 45, Folder 465)
      - Preparation in Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry for Medical Sciences, Committee on, (1929-1930?) (Box 45, Folder 466)
      - Prizes, undated (Box 45, Folder 467)
      - Reorganization of the Sheffield Scientific School, Committee Appointed to Consider, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 468)
      - Research in Fields of Physical Science and Engineering, Committee on, 1940-1943 (Box 45, Folder 469)
      - Robinson Foundation, 1945-1946, 1948, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 470)
      - Science and Engineering at Yale, Committee to Investigate the Problems of (Henry S. Graves, chairman), 1930-1932 (Box 46, Folder 471 - 472)
      - Science and Mathematics, Division of See also: folder.449, Department of Mathematics, 1933-1945 (Box 46, Folder 473)
      - Science departments, histories of, 1933, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 474)
      - Secretary's Office, Yale University: correspondence with Marion L. Phillips, 1929, 1932, 1936, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 475)
      - Selective Service, Committee on, 1940-1944 (Box 46, Folder 476)
      - Seymour, Charles, President of Yale University, 1937-1950 (Box 46, Folder 477)
      - Sheffield (Amelia Daggett) Fund See: folder 479, Joseph Earl Sheffield Room
      - Sheffield (George) Scholarship, 1941-1942, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 478)
      - Sheffield (Joseph Earl) Room (funded by the Amelia Daggett Sheffield Fund), 1934-1937, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 479)
      - Sheffield Scientific School, history of: various sketches by C.H. Warren, Director and others, 1945, 1947, undated (Box 46, Folder 480)
      - Sheffield Scientific School: memo re: its termination as an active school, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 481)
      - Social Research, Dean's Committee on: reports and correspondence with H. B. Fisher of the Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1936-1945 (Box 46, Folder 482)
      - Strathcona Hall, 1931-1934, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 483)
      - Student Council, 1925, undated (Box 46, Folder 484)
      - Student Preparation for War Service Committee: minutes and records, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 485)
      - Summer Session, Yale University, 1945-1946 (Box 47, Folder 486)
      - Tinker Committee See: folder 436, Committee to Consider the Position of the Humanities
      - Torch Honor Society, 1926-1928, 1930, 1932 (Box 47, Folder 487)
      - Treasurer's Office, Yale University: correspondence with Horace F. Isleib, 1954-1955 (Box 47, Folder 488)
      - Treasurer's Office, Yale University: correspondence with H. J. Ostrander, 1927-1943 (Box 47, Folder 489)
      - Trustees of Sheffield Scientific School: general business, 1932, 1936-1938 (Box 47, Folder 490)
      - Trustees of Sheffield Scientific School: Thomas Farnam, Treasurer, 1930, 1942-1943 (Box 47, Folder 491)
      - Trustees of Sheffield Scientific School: information re: Silliman College which absorbed Sheffield Scientific School's Vanderbilt dormitory, 1938, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 492)
      - Tyler, Parker R. (1929S): correspondence re: a small fund in honor of Miss Colburn, 1940, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 493)
      - Undergraduate Schools Reorganization, President's Committee on, 1927-1928 (Box 47, Folder 494)
      - University Reorganization, Joint Committee on, (consisting of the Governing Board of Sheffield Scientific School and the Permanent Officers of Yale College), 1918-1920 (Box 47, Folder 495 - 496)
      - Whittlesey, Charles W.: correspondence re: setting up a fund for Sheffield Scientific School lectures and research in the chemistry of photography, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 497)
      - Yale Engineering Association See also: folders 408-413, Engineering Camp, East Lyme, 1919-1925 (Box 47, Folder 498)
      - Yale Natural Preserve, Committee on See: folder 454, Committee on Yale Natural Preserve
      - Zoological Laboratory: list of books deposited by Sheffield Scientific School, 1914 January (Box 47, Folder 499)
      - Zoology, 1934, 1937, 1940 (Box 47, Folder 500)
    - Personnel Records
      - Benson, Adolph B., Professor of German and Scandinavian, 1920, 1923, 1931, 1932 (Box 48, Folder 501)
      - Chemistry, Department of: faculty appointments, 1926-1946 (Box 48, Folder 502)
      - Clarke, Charles Cameron, Professor of French, 1929 (Box 48, Folder 503)
      - Crane, Theodore, Associate Professor of Building Construction, 1924, 1927, 1930 (Box 48, Folder 504)
      - Crawford, Jack Randall, Professor of English, 1922-1941 (Box 48, Folder 505)
      - Curtis, Harry Alfred, Professor of Chemical Engineering, 1923, 1927-1930 (Box 48, Folder 506)
      - Dauber, Carl F., Assistant Professor of Plant Physiology, 1926-1941 (Box 48, Folder 507)
      - Doherty, Robert Ernest, Dean of the School of Engineering, 1931-1935 (Box 48, Folder 508)
      - Economics faculty appointments, 1925-1945 (Box 48, Folder 509)
      - Engineering Camp, East Lyme: agreements and correspondence with Claus G. Duberg, caretaker, 1931, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 510)
      - English: faculty appointments, 1920-1936 (Box 48, Folder 511)
      - Engstrom, Howard T., Associate Professor of Mathematics, 1931-1945 (Box 48, Folder 512)
      - Evans, Alexander William, Eaton Professor of Botany, 1922, 1924, 1928, 1934, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 513)
      - Getting, Ivan Alexander, Assistant Professor of Physics, 1941-1945 (Box 48, Folder 514)
      - Goedicke, Victor, Instructor of Astronomy, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 515)
      - Hall, Marshall, Assistant Professor of Mathematics, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 516)
      - Hart, Frank H., 1941 (Box 48, Folder 517)
      - Hastings, Hudson Bridge (Box 48, Folder 518)
      - Haverneyer, Loomis, Associate Dean of Sheffield Scientific School and Registrar of the School of Engineering, 1923-1945 (Box 48, Folder 519)
      - Healy, Kent T., Assistant Professor of Transportation, 1936 (Box 48, Folder 520)
      - Herrington, L.P., Director of Research of the John B. Pierce Laboratory of Hygiene, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 521)
      - Johnson, Trent Baldwin, Sterling Professor of Chemistry, 1921-1923, 1926, 1928, 1935-1936, 1940-1941 (Box 48, Folder 522)
      - Jones, Ralph Coughenour, Associate Professor of Economics, 1924-1940 (Box 48, Folder 523)
      - Kovarick, Alois Francis, Associate Professor of Physics, 1924-1927 (Box 48, Folder 524)
      - Lull, Dorothy: correspondence re: her chances of employment, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 525)
      - Mathematics, Department of: material turned over to Dean Sinnott by Dean Warren, 1940-1944 (Box 49, Folder 526)
      - Mendall, Lafayette Benedict, Sterling Professor of Physiological Chemistry, memorial exercises, 1936 (Box 49, Folder 527)
      - Miller, John Perry, Assistant Professor of Economics, 1939-1940 (Box 49, Folder 528)
      - Millikan, Max Franklin, Research Associate in Economics, 1942-1945 (Box 49, Folder 529)
      - Montgomery, Deane, re: appointment in Mathematics Department, 1946-1947 (Box 49, Folder 530)
      - Murphy, George Moseley, Associate Professor of Chemistry, 1936-1948 (Box 49, Folder 531)
      - Personnel Study and Bureau of Appointments, Yale University Department of, 1938-1944 (Box 49, Folder 532)
      - Petrunkevitch, Alexander, Professor of Zoology, 1922-1925, 1935, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 533)
      - Physics, Department of See also: folder 550, John Zeleny
      - Physics, Department of: faculty appointments, 1940-1952 (Box 49, Folder 534 - 535)
      - Saxon, Olin Glenn, Professor of Economics, 1931-1945 (Box 49, Folder 536)
      - Scott, Walter, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 537)
      - Smith, Elliot Dunlop, Professor of Industrial Relations, 1928-1938 (Box 49, Folder 538)
      - Smith, Percy Franklin, Professor of Mathematics, 1922-1930 (Box 49, Folder 539)
      - Speng, Kenneth M., Assistant Professor of Economics, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 540)
      - Spitzer, Lyman Jr., Research Associate in Astrophysics, 1944-1945 (Box 49, Folder 541)
      - Tatum, Edward Lawrie, Associate Professor of Chemistry, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 542)
      - Uhler, Horace Scudder, Professor of Physics, 1926-1939, 1942 (Box 49, Folder 543)
      - Vance, John Edward, Associate Professor of Chemistry, 1932-1948 (Box 49, Folder 544)
      - Van Name, Ralph Gibbs, Associate Professor of Chemistry, 1933 (Box 49, Folder 545)
      - [illegible], 1945 (Box 49)
      - Waterman, Alan Tower, Associate Professor of Physics, 1933-1948 (Box 49, Folder 546)
      - Whittemore, James Kelsey, Associate Professor of Mathematics, 1926-1942 (Box 49, Folder 547)
      - Wood, Scott Emerson, Assistant Professor of Chemistry, 1940-1948 (Box 49, Folder 548)
      - Woodruff, Lorande Loss, Professor of Protozoology, 1936-1944 (Box 49, Folder 549)
      - Zeleny, John, Chairman of the Department of Physics, 1928-1939 (Box 49, Folder 550)
  - Annual Reports
    - 1925-1926 (Box 50, Folder 551)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 50, Folder 552)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 50, Folder 553)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 50, Folder 554)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 555)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 50, Folder 556)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 50, Folder 557)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 50, Folder 558)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 50, Folder 559)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 50, Folder 560)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 50, Folder 561)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 50, Folder 562)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 50, Folder 563)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 50, Folder 564)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 50, Folder 565)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 50, Folder 566)
    - 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 567)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 50, Folder 569)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 50, Folder 570)
  - Committee on the Selection of a Successor to Sheffield Scientific School Director Russell H. Chittenden
    - Correspondence, notes, 1921 October-1922 May (Box 51, Folder 571)
  - Appointing Board Records
    - Appointing Board and Connecticut State Board of Visitors: minutes, 1864 July 5-1894 June 26 (Box 52, Folder 572)
    - Lists of state scholars, 1892-1894 (Box 52, Folder 573)
    - Miscellaneous papers re: board business and state scholars, 1890-1891, 1892-1894 (Box 52, Folder 574)
  - Semi-centennial Celebration, 1897
    - Correspondence
      - A (Box 53, Folder 575)
      - Ba-Bl (Box 53, Folder 576)
      - Bo-Bu (Box 53, Folder 577)
      - C (Box 53, Folder 578)
      - D (Box 53, Folder 579)
      - E (Box 53, Folder 580)
      - F (Box 53, Folder 581)
      - G (Box 53, Folder 582)
      - Ha-Hi (Box 53, Folder 583)
      - Ho-Hu (Box 53, Folder 584)
      - I (Box 53, Folder 585)
      - J (Box 53, Folder 586)
      - K (Box 53, Folder 587)
      - L (Box 53, Folder 588)
      - M (Box 53, Folder 589)
      - N (Box 53, Folder 590)
      - O (Box 53, Folder 591)
      - P (Box 53, Folder 592)
      - Q-R (Box 54, Folder 593)
      - S (Box 54, Folder 594)
      - T (Box 54, Folder 595)
      - U-V (Box 54, Folder 596)
      - Wa-We (Box 54, Folder 597)
      - Wh-Wu (Box 54, Folder 598)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 54, Folder 599)
    - Bartlett John P. (1898S): typescript of address given at Sheffield Scientific School semi-centennial alumni meeting (Box 54, Folder 600)
    - Brinley, Charles A. (18698): typescript of address given at Sheffield Scientific School semi-centennial alumni meeting (Box 54, Folder 601)
    - Jenkins, Dr. Edward H. (1872S): manuscript address given at Sheffield Scientific School semi-centennial alumni meeting (Box 54, Folder 602)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence and lists of Sheffield Scientific School graduates and non-graduates (Box 54, Folder 603)
    - Guest book containing signatures and remarks of Dr. Edward H. Jenkins (1872S), Charles A. Brinley (18698) and John P. Bartlett (1878S) at the alumni meeting (Box 55, Folder 604)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1947
    - Convocation Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 56, Folder 605)
    - Correspondence, congratulatory (Box 56, Folder 606)
    - Correspondence, general (Box 56, Folder 607)
    - Gibbs, Josiah Willard: correspondence re: book published about him in conjunction with Sheffield Scientific School centennial (Box 56, Folder 608)
    - Pamphlet # 1, "Generations of Great Teachers", 1946 (Box 56, Folder 609)
    - Pamphlet # 2, "Science and the Humanities", 1946-1947 (Box 56, Folder 610)
    - Haggard, Howard W.: correspondence re: centennial pamphlet # 2 (Box 56, Folder 611)
    - Press book (Box 56, Folder 612)
    - Proceedings: soundscriber discs (Box 56, Folder 613)
    - Publicity: correspondence (Box 56, Folder 614 - 615)
    - Publicity: news releases, news programs and articles (Box 57, Folder 616)
    - Publicity:Yale Alumni Magazine article re: Sheffield Scientific School Centennial Celebration, 1946 May-1947 November (Box 57, Folder 617)
    - Silliman Lecture Committee: correspondence, lists, minutes, 1946-1947 (Box 57, Folder 618)
    - Committee on Arrangements Louis Havemeyer, Chairman
      - Acceptances: lists of arrangements (Box 58, Folder 619)
      - Banquet, meals: correspondence, lists, arrangements (Box 58, Folder 620)
      - Banquet menu (Box 58, Folder 621)
      - Banquet table (Box 58, Folder 622)
      - Centennial weekend program (Box 58, Folder 623)
      - Convocation program (Box 58, Folder 624)
      - Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 625)
      - Correspondence and work papers re: arrangements (Box 58, Folder 626)
      - Dinner guest lists, individuals in different fields of science (Box 58, Folder 627)
      - Invitations, response cards, tickets (Box 58, Folder 628)
      - Money matters (Box 58, Folder 629)
      - Minutes: Sheffield Centennial Committee and meetings of the Chairmen of Subcommittees (Box 58, Folder 630)
      - Response cards: individuals representing various colleges, universities, institutions, scientific and learned societies (Box 58, Folder 631)
      - Response cards: Yale representatives to the Centennial ceremonies (Box 58, Folder 632)
  - Student Registers
    - 1861-1864 (Box 59, Folder 633 - 634)
  - Official Notices
    - 1860s-1880s (Box 60, Folder 635)
    - 1890s (Box 60, Folder 636)
    - 1889-1900 (Box 60, Folder 637)
    - 1900-1901 (Box 60, Folder 638)
    - 1901-1902 (Box 60, Folder 639)
    - 1902-1903 (Box 60, Folder 640)
    - 1903-1904 (Box 60, Folder 641)
    - 1904-1905 (Box 60, Folder 642)
    - 1905-1906 (Box 60, Folder 643)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 60, Folder 644)
    - 1907-1908 (Box 60, Folder 645)
    - 1998-1909 (Box 60, Folder 646)
    - 1909-1910 (Box 60, Folder 647)
    - 1910-1911 (Box 60, Folder 648)
    - 1911-1912 (Box 60, Folder 649)
    - 1912-1913 (Box 60, Folder 650)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 60, Folder 651)
    - 1914-1915 (Box 60, Folder 652)
    - 1915-1916 (Box 60, Folder 653)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 60, Folder 654)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 60, Folder 655)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 60, Folder 656)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 60, Folder 657)
    - 1920-1921 (Box 60, Folder 658)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 61, Folder 659)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 61, Folder 660)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 61, Folder 661)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 61, Folder 662)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 61, Folder 663)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 61, Folder 664)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 61, Folder 665)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 62, Folder 666)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 62, Folder 667)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 62, Folder 668)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 62, Folder 669)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 62, Folder 670)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 133)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 62, Folder 672)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 62, Folder 673)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 62, Folder 674)